In this exercise, we're gonna look at tabs and tabs navigation,
在这个练习中 我们将介绍选项卡和选项卡导航
and how we can make use of that on our website.
以及如何在我们的网站中使用
So we'll go back to the website that we have been working on so far, and
我们将返回我们目前开发的网站
add tab navigation to one part of about our aboutus.html page.
并在 aboutus.html 页面中 添加选项卡导航
So let's quickly visit the current state of the aboutus.html page, and
现在我们来快速查看 当前的 aboutus.html 页面
identify where we can introduce tabs and tab navigation.
以识别在何处引入选项卡和选项卡导航
Taking a look at the aboutus.html page.
看一下 aboutus.html 页面
As we scroll down we notice that this
当我们往下拉  我们注意到
location where we have the list of corporate leadership at our restaurant.
在这里我们有一个我们餐厅 领导层的列表
Provides an excellent opportunity for us to apply tabs and tab navigation.
这是我们使用选项卡和 选项卡导航的绝好机会
Now we can use tabs to separate out the content from
现在我们可使用选项卡分离
each of the corporate leadership members.
每一公司领导的简介
And then use tab navigation to navigate Between the different
然后使用选项卡导航
profiles of the different members there.
在各个成员的简介间切换
To introduce tab navigation to the aboutus.html page,
为了在 aboutus.html 页面中 加入选项卡导航
add the location that we identified, let's go to the HTML code in brackets.
在我们刚刚设想的位置 我们转向 brackets 中的 HTML 代码
And scroll down to the location where
我们向下滚动至
we need to introduce the tabs and tab navigation.
我们需要加入选项卡和选项卡导航的位置
Here you can see that I have already introduced
这里你可看到我已经讲过的
the part of the code that is required to setup the tab navigation.
构建选项卡导航所需的代码
So let's go and look at the result of this on the web page.
我们先看下这段代码 在网页上呈现的结果
And then we'll come back and examine this code.
接下来我们再回来 查看这段代码
Going to the webpage you'll now notice that just below the corporate
在网页上你会注意到就在 "Corporate Leadership"下
leadership we now have tab elements in place.
各选项卡已经就位
This has been introduced by the code that we added to the about us HTML page.
这就是我们刚在 aboutus.html 页面 加入的那段代码
In particular notice how this tab navigation works.
仔细观察这个选项卡导航如何工作
So you can click on any one of these tabs in order to switch between the tabs.
你可以点击任何一个选项卡 以在选项卡间进行切换
Now, obviously as I switched between the tabs,
显而易见 现在当我在选项卡间切换时
nothing happened, because we haven't introduced the rest of the code
什么都没发生 因为我们还没有添加剩下的代码
to enable us to separate the content into different tabs.
以便将内容放入不同的选项卡
And then when we click on the tabs,
添加完这些代码后 再点击选项卡
we should be able to navigate to the different tabs.
我们将能浏览不同的选项卡
Going back to the source code, you'll notice that the tab elements there
返回到源代码 你会注意到这里的选项卡
have been constructed using the ul class
由 ul 标签构建
with the nav and nav-tabs as their class for
使用 nav 和 nav-tabs 作为其类属性
the ul and of course, the role that we have given this tablist.
使用 tablist 作为其角色属性
Now, inside this ul, a list elements specify
在这个 ul 标签中 各列表项具体实现了
the various tabs that will form part of this tab navigation.
将要组成选项卡导航的各个选项卡
So let's go in and look at the individual list elements and
我们到 ul 中 查看各个列表项
then identify the various parts that are specified in those list of elements.
然后识别这些列表项的各个属性
So going down we see that the first list element corresponds to the tab for
在下面我们看到第一个列表项 对应于
the CEO of the company.
公司CEO这个选项卡
In here we specify for the list.
在这里我们定义列表项
We specify the class as active.
我们设置其类属性为 active
Which means that this is the tab that the users will see when
此设置说明这一选项卡 将是可见的
they first navigate down to that location on the webpage.
在用户首次浏览到 网页的这个位置时
The remaining tabs will be hidden behind the scene and
而其它选项卡是隐藏的
they users can navigate to those tabs by clicking on
用户可以前往这些选项卡
the tab items in the tab navigation.
只要点击选项卡导航上的选项
In addition, inside the list item we have a a tag
此外在列表项中有一个 a 标签
which contains the actual content of the list item there.
包含有列表项的实际内容
So this a tag contains the href that we're gonna make use of to refer to the specific
这个 a 标签的 href 属性 用于指向具体的选项卡内容
tab item, which will be included as part of this tab.
选项卡内容将会作为选项卡的一部分
We'll talk about how we include the tab content in the next step, but
我们将在接下来的步骤中谈到 如何加入选项卡内容
you notice that I have already introduced the link to that tab content.
你看到我已经加入了 指向选项卡内容的链接
So, what is left is for me to design the tab content and
所以剩下的就是 设计选项卡内容
then specify the appropriate link for the tab content.
并为选项卡内容设定合适的链接
In addition, there are specifying that the data toggle is a tab, so
此外 还有一个 data-toggle 属性 值为 tab
this way we know that we are activating the JavaScript component
这样我们知道我们正在使用 JavaScript 组件
that enables support to the tab navigation.
以支持选项卡导航
Looking at the remaining list items in this
看下 ul 标签中的其它列表项
ul here, you'll notice that for the remaining ones also,
你将注意到这些列表项
the specification is similar in the a tag you specify the ID
的实现方法是类似的 a 标签指向
of the tab content element, that we are going to introduce later.
选项卡内容的 id 我们后续会看到
Now that we have constructed the navigation part of the tabbed design.
现在我们已经构建了 选项卡设计的导航部分
Let's look at how we're gonna take the actual content and
接下来要把实际内容
enclose them inside tabs.
放入选项卡中
So to do that, let's scroll down and
要做到这一点 向下滚动
then we see that we have the content down below here.
我们看到在这下方 有需要包含入选项卡的内容
We want to separate this content into four different tabs, so that when the user
我们将其分开放入4个不同的选项卡窗格
clicks on one of those tabs then they user will be able to navigate to that
这样当用户点击其中的一个选项卡时 用户就能浏览
specific tab containing the details of the person selected from the tab navigation.
从选项卡导航中选择人员 的详细信息
To divide the content into multiple tab panes,
要将内容分开 放入多个选项卡窗格
the first thing that we do is to enclose the entire content
首先我们要做的是 将所有内容
into a div with the class tab-content.
放入一个带有 tab-content 类属性的 div 标签
Now, then after we will introduce tab panes,
现在我们将介绍选项卡窗格
which will contain individual items that correspond to each of the tabs
选项卡窗格包含对应每个选项卡 的各个条目
that have been identified in the tab navigation that we have already set up.
这些选项卡已经在我们构建的 选项卡导航中列出
We set up the content for each tab pane by enclosing
为了构建选项卡窗格
the content inside a dev which is given the class
我们把选项卡窗格对应的内容 放入一个 div 标签中
tab-pane as you see in the code there.
这个标签的类属性为 tab-pane 如这里的代码所示
Now for this class, aside from tab-pane I have also specified the fade and the in.
这个标签的类属性除了 tab-pane 还有 fade 和 in
fade meaning that when you transition to this tab, then this tab will fade in,.
fade 表示当你转入这个选项卡时 将有一个淡入的效果
So we introduce some transitions into the web page so
这样我们在网页中引入了过渡
that when you're navigating to different parts,
当你在转入不同部位时
the navigation, the movement looks fluid on the screen.
浏览动作看起来流畅
The in part is to identify that this tab should be left open
类 in 表示这个选项卡窗格应该可见
when the user first navigates to this part of the webpage.
在用户首次浏览到该网页的这个位置时
So in this case, we will have the first tab corresponding to the CEO always
这样，我们将对应于CEO的 首个选项卡窗格
open when the user first navigates down to this part of the webpage.
设置为可见 当用户首次浏览到该网页的这个位置时
So subsequently the user can select the remaining tabs by clicking on the tab
接下来用户可以点击选项卡
items there.
选择前往其余的选项卡窗格
We are now going to repeat the same for the remaining content in here.
对这里剩余的内容 我们重复同样的操作
After we complete that, then we'll go and look at the new state of the pitch.
做完这些 我们再看一下现在的页面
After enclosing all the content respectively
在将所有内容分别封入
into their respective tab page, Let's go and look at the resulting webpage.
各自的选项卡窗格后 我们看下完成的网页
Moving back to our webpage,
回到我们的网页
you now notice that the content has been neatly organized into tabs there.
可以看到内容已被 整洁的放入各个选项卡窗格
We have now separated each of the content into the individual dibs
现在我们已经将内容分别放入 各自的 div 标签
with the class tab page.
div 标签带有类属性 tab-pane
And attached them appropriately to the tab
至于如何将这些选项卡窗格
navigation elements that are part of the tab navigation that we already introduced.
和选项卡导航元素相连 我们已经讲过
No when we'll click on the are tabs,
现在当我们点击选项卡时
the content will appropriately switch to show the corresponding content.
其中的内容会正确切换 以显示对应的内容
Now, for each of these tab pages, we have appropriately set up the IDs so
现在对每个选项卡窗格 我们都设置了 id 属性
that the links that have been introduced for
这样 我们为选项卡导航元素
these tab- navigation image there will work correctly.
设立的链接就可正确工作
One last minor change that we would like to introduce here
我们将要介绍的最后 一处小改动是
is to enclose this content inside a pane
把所有内容放入
with actual borders to introduce the pane so that it looks like a real tab here.
一个带边框的窗格中 这样会看起来像一个真正的选项卡
I'm going to go in and introduce some minor changes
我将介绍一些小改动
to the tab content element what we have described.
针对我们介绍过的选项卡内容
To introduce borders for the tab content I'm
为了给选项卡内容加上边框
gonna go into the mystyles.html page and
打开文件 mystyles.css
set up the appropriate code for the tab content page there.
为选项卡内容加入合适的代码
So looking at the code here, you'll see that I have set up the CSS class for
看下这里的代码 你将看到我为选项卡内容加了
the tab content to include borders on the left, right,
一个 CSS 类 设置了选项卡内容的
and the bottom of the tab content with a padding of ten pixels.
左侧、右侧和底边边框 同时设置内边距为 10 像素
Now this will complete the look and feel of the tab content,
这样选项卡的外观感觉 就圆满了
such that it looks really like tabs there.
看起来真正像选项卡
Going back to our webpage, you now notice that the content of the tab
回到我们的网页 你将看到选项卡窗格中的内容
panes are now enclosed neatly inside bolded tabs and
整洁地包含在 带有边框的选项卡中
they have connected themselves to the tab navigation elements appropriately.
选项卡导航元素中的链接 正确指向选项卡内容
So that it looks like a real tab.
这样看起来像一个真正的选项卡
So when you navigate to the different tabs.
这样当你浏览不同的选项卡时
You do notice a nice, clean interface being delivered for these tabs there.
你会看到一个友好整齐的界面
This completes the exercise on using tabs.
使用选项卡的练习到此圆满结束
So in this exercise, we examined tabs and tab navigation, and how we can,
在这个练习中 我们细致学习了选项卡和选项卡导航
put content into tab panes, and then appropriately associated those tab panes.
以及如何把内容放入选项卡窗格 并正确建立这些窗格
With the tab navigation elements, so that the navigation works correctly.
与选项卡导航元素间的联系 以便导航能正确工作
Now, obviously as we have stated earlier, for the tab navigation to work,
显而易见如我们先前的声明 为了让选项卡导航正确工作
you need JavaScript component to be included into your web page.
你需要在网页中引用 JavaScript 组件
We have already included the bootstrap.min.js file there.
我们已经在页面中引用了 bootstrap.min.js 文件
So that's why this JavaScript plugin is already included into our webpage.
这就是我们已经在网页中引用 这一 JavaScript 插件的原因